hawkeslearning.com 2010-01-02

# Hawkes Learning Systems

(last updated: March 28, 2003) 

Quant Systems Inc. is committed to protecting your privacy. This Quant Systems Inc. Statement of Privacy applies to Quant Systems Inc.'s family of Web sites and governs data collection and usage at all Quant Systems Inc. sites and services; it does not apply to other online or offline Quant Systems Inc. sites, products or services. Please read the Quant Systems Inc. Statement of Privacy below and also any supplementary information at the end of this statement for additional details about particular Quant Systems Inc. sites and services that you may use.

Quant Systems Inc. is a general audience web site, intended for users of all ages. Personal information of all users is collected, used and disclosed as described in this Statement of Privacy.

At some sites, Quant Systems Inc. collects personal information, such as your e-mail address, name, or telephone number. 

Quant Systems Inc. also collects certain information about your computer hardware and software. This information may include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by Quant Systems Inc. for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of Quant Systems Inc..

Quant Systems Inc. keeps track of the pages our customers visit within Quant Systems Inc., in order to determine what Quant Systems Inc. sites and services are the most popular. This data is also used by Quant Systems Inc. to deliver customized content.

Quant Systems Inc. encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from Quant Systems Inc. so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. Quant Systems Inc. is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the Quant Systems Inc. and Quant Systems Inc. family of Web sites.

Quant Systems Inc. and its operational service partners collect and use your personal information to operate Quant Systems Inc. and deliver the services you have requested. Quant Systems Inc. also uses your personal information to inform you of other products or services available from Quant Systems Inc. and its affiliates. Quant Systems Inc. may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

Quant Systems Inc. does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent. For "course management sites" that provide materials and services to instructors and students for purposes of specific courses or testing, the site may display the names, email addresses, grades and log-in names in instructor grade books and make them available to school administrators. Instructors can use student email addresses for communication with students regarding the course and administrators may store personal data generated by the course site tools for the purpose of maintaining educational records or other legitimate educational purposes.

Quant Systems Inc. may access and/or disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Quant Systems Inc. or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Quant Systems Inc., including its Quant Systems Inc. family of Web sites; or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Quant Systems Inc., its web sites, or the public.

Personal information collected on this site may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Quant Systems Inc. or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using this site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. Quant Systems Inc. abides by the safe harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union.

Quant Systems Inc. is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer systems with limited access, which are located in controlled facilities. When we transmit highly confidential information (such as a credit card number) over the Internet, we protect it through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

Quant Systems Inc. collects information during the registration process. The personal information Quant Systems Inc. collects includes first and last name. In addition, Quant Systems Inc. also collects the following information for service reasons: e-mail address, phone number, school, term, and school year. 

Your registration information is used to operate the site, and to provide the user with the best technical service possible. New users that provide an e-mail address will receive a Quant Systems Inc. welcome letter explaining the usage of their access code and how to utilize the “access.cod” file. 

Quant Systems Inc. will not share your e-mail address with any business partners, or third party members.

Quant Systems Inc. is concerned about controlling unsolicited commercial e-mail. Quant Systems Inc. will not sell, lease or rent its member lists to any third parties. While Quant Systems Inc. continues to actively review and implement new technology, such as expanded filtering features, there is no currently available technology that will totally prevent the sending and receiving of unsolicited e-mail.

Quant Systems Inc. uses "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. For example, if you personalize Quant Systems Inc.'s pages, or register with Quant Systems Inc. sites or services, a cookie helps Quant Systems Inc. to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as access code, WebCMS address, and so on. When you return to Quant Systems Inc., the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Quant Systems Inc. features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Quant Systems Inc. services or Web sites you visit. 

If you have questions regarding this statement, you should first contact Quant Systems Inc. via e-mail. If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should then contact Quant Systems Inc. via telephone at (843) 571-2825.

Quant Systems Inc. will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. If there are material changes to this Statement or in how Quant Systems Inc. will use your personal information, Quant Systems Inc. will prominently post such changes prior to implementing the change. Quant Systems Inc. encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Quant Systems Inc. is protecting your information.

Quant Systems Inc. welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Quant Systems Inc. has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Quant Systems Inc. by telephone, e-mail, or postal mail.

Quant Systems Inc.  
1023 Wappoo Rd. Suite 6A  
Charleston, SC 29407  
(843) 571-2825
